I was glad to see you guys got a dollar
store up the street because my
anniversary today so I had to get a few
things I kind of her a couple things I'm
such a sucker for that dollar store oh
no I always shop there trying to save
money
last summer I bought this gigantic can
of ant spray use the entire can trying
to kill nine ants the only ones that
died with ones that couldn't swim so
that is dollar store today I'm not
giving over there get some other stuff
and done I got all these items and the
cashier is like scanning stuff at the
dollar store one I won't go through
keeps trying it I'm thinking she calls
for a price check I'm going to punch it
[Laughter]
she keeps trying and finally I'm like
pretty sure it's a dollar and the people
who shop they're just as bad how many
times you been the dollar store of
somebody going how much is this I think
it's the dollar store can you memorize
that one time I fit it right to their
face I got fire but it was worth it